dcielts.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy |

PRIVACY POLICY

Please be assured that I will guard your privacy

Privacy Policy for www.dcielts.com and www.dcielts-learning-centre.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about my privacy policy, please feel free to contact me by email at dcielts@gmail.com

The privacy of my visitors is extremely important to me. This privacy policy document outlines what kinds of personal information are received and collected by www.dcielts.com and how they are used.

Log Files  
Like most other Web sites, www.dcielts.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.dcielts.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customise Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

<a href=”http://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/419628″ title=”Privacy Policy”>Privacy Policy</a><script type=”text/javascript”>(function (w,d) {var loader = function () {var s = d.createElement(“script”), tag = d.getElementsByTagName(“script”)[0]; s.src = “http://cdn.iubenda.com/iubenda.js”; tag.parentNode.insertBefore(s,tag);}; if(w.addEventListener){w.addEventListener(“load”, loader, false);}else if(w.attachEvent){w.attachEvent(“onload”, loader);}else{w.onload = loader;}})(window, document);</script>

If I have helped you with these ideas and resources, please share them  
1300
